# **DJURO ALFIREVIC**

Belgrade, Serbia djalfirevic@gmail.com +381 64 1 84 74 84

## **Summary**

Senior iOS Engineer with over 15 years in iOS development. Background includes iOS, macOS, .NET, Java, PHP, React and React Native development working in an Agile work environment. Complete iOS portfolio: <u>link</u>. Personal website: <u>link</u>.

# **Key Skills**

Languages/technologies/frameworks: Objective-C, Swift, React, React Native, Java, .NET, C#, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Agile, Scrum, Git

## **Work Experience**

Reddit: iOS Lead @ Profiles

July 2021 -

- Working as an iOS Lead

Medable: Senior Software Engineer

June 2019 - June 2021

- Worked as a Senior iOS Engineer

Flightradar24: Senior iOS Engineer

October 2017 - June 2019

- Worked as a Senior iOS Engineer

**Cubes: Director of Engineering / CTO** 

September 2015 - September 2017

- Worked as an iOS Lead
- Worked as a Software Engineering Manager/Project Manager/CTO

#### Ministry of Defense: Senior Software Engineer September 2006 - August 2015

- Worked on full software development lifecycle (.NET, Java)
- Worked as a Chief Software Architect
- Worked as a Software Engineering Manager

#### Education

Masters Degree 2001 - 2006

Military Academy, MSc Software Engineering